my chains - This is my Freedom this is my choice of
мои цепи - Это моя Свобода это мой выбор
chain Yes really
цепи Да реально
rap
рап
Hello Hello I'm from the city of
Здравствуйте Здравствуйте я из города
Khmelnitsky Where are you from I'm from St.
Хмельницкий Вы откуда Я из
Petersburg
Петербурга прикольно
cool Yeah Well I asked what I was interested in Well
Угу Ну я спросил что Меня интересовало
maybe you have questions oh well
Ну может у вас есть вопросы а хорошо У
I only have questions somewhere closer to  the
меня есть вопросы только где-то ближе к
microphone is very hard to
микрофону очень плохо
hear, you know, I’m interested in the role of
слышно знаете меня интересует роль
democracy and the role of ochlocracy in
демократии и роль охлократии в
modern society, you’re interested in this
современном обществе вас это интересует
and the substitution of the substitution of these two concepts
и подмена подмена двух этих понятий
when democracy is replaced by ochlocracy,
когда демократию подменяют охлократии
so you once lived in an
вот вы жили когда-то в
ochlocracy society,
охлократии обществе
well, well, did you live or not
что ну ну жили или нет
once I live now in  in a democratic
когда-то Я живу сейчас в демократическом
society, my ancestors once lived in human
обществе мои предки когда-то жили че
society, but can you tell me what criteria for a
общест а можете какие критерии
democratic
демократического
society are the power of the people and democratic
общества власть народа и демократические
procedures? Yes, manifestations of this power, that
процедуры Да проявления этой власти то
is, there are elections, referendums, and so on.
есть там выборы референдум и так Дале
That’s interesting. You’re definitely from
Вот вот интересно Вы точно из
St. Petersburg, of course, yes, that is,
санкт-петербурга конечно да то есть у
you have them there  Well, as I understand it, it’s
вас там есть Ну я так понимаю что
correct that in Russia now there is power of
правильно что в России сейчас власть
the people,
народа
yes yes. And about the referendum elections, you can
да да А про выборы референдум можете
tell me how they happen there, I
рассказать как они у вас там происходят
know you had this one, what was his
вот зна у вас был какой-то этот как его
name, Alexander or Alexey Alexey
звали Александр или Алексей Алексей
Navalny He wanted to go to the elections in 2018
Навальный Он хотел на выборы идти в 2018
year, if I’m not mistaken, yes, because, well,
году если я не ошибаюсь да потому что ну
free elections are democratic, yes, but they
свободный выборы же демократические да а
didn’t let him in and they put him in jail,
его не пустили ещё и посадили было такое
or not, or did it seem to me because he’s a
или нет или мне показалось потому что он
criminal or something, I just didn’t happen,
преступник что ли не не я просто не было
yes, he wasn’t allowed to vote because of a
такого его не пустили на выборы вот изза
violation  which he committed in his
нарушения которые он допустил в своём
past Yeah and What violations were
прошлом Ага а Какие нарушения были у
he violating he violated the law like
него нарушение он закон нарушил как
what Well, if you can ask a criminal case
какой Ну если вы можете уголовное дело
you are in this
поинтересоваться вы вы в этом
democratic society I just can’t
демократическом обществе Я просто не
understand he was a politician Yes he is
могу понять он был политиком Да
anti-corruption As I understand it
антикоррупционное Я так понимаю
or is it FC Tom  that it’s
или это ФК том что
not the Armed Forces who poisoned the truth, this is your
отравили не это ВС правда вот ваша
reality, this is the Armed Forces great
реальность это ВС пра
Boo You’re running away from this one because
Бу Вот ты убегаешь из этой те потому что
it’s a sore
она больная
subject, it’s a sore subject because
обю боя тема больная тема потому что
democracy is a change of power No, this is the
демократия это сменяемость власти Нет
choice of the people, this is the choice of the people, that’s
это это выбор народа это выбо народа вот
how you don’t have the choice of the people  because
так у вас нету выбора народа потому что
your choice is artificial because you are
выбор у вас искусственные потому что вас
not allowed candidates who can
не допускают кандидатов которые могут
compete Yes, they draw
составить конкуренцию Да вот и рисуют
whatever you want Yes, that’s why you
всё что вам захочется Да поэтому вы
live what you want Everything is absolutely
живёте что вам захочется Совершенно
correct You live in a slave country Yes
верно всё Вы живёте в рабской стране Да
in a slave country but you make a mask that you are
в рабской стране но делаете маску что вы
in the Democratic  you look funny you
в Демократической вы смешно выглядае вы
look funny really yes rap who
смешно выглядите реально да рап который
says
говорит
that my chains are my Freedom this is my
что мои цепи - Это моя Свобода это мой
choice of chain Yes really rap It’s just that there are
выбор цепи Да реально рап Просто есть
people from the Russian Federation who
люди вот из Российской Федерации которые
Yes they say I can’t go out Here come on
Да они говорят я не могу выйти Вот давай
free country I’m in the city of Khmelnitsk
свободная страна Я в городе Хмельницке
you’re in  in the city of St. Petersburg Tomorrow we will go out
ты в городе Сант Петербург Завтра выйдем
with an empty piece of paper to the central
с пустым листочком на центральную
square and stand for 15 minutes just with
площадь и постоим 15 минут просто с
an empty white piece of paper in silence you
пустым белым листком молча сможешь
can stand for 15 minutes I can m the problem let's
простоять 15 минут смогу м проблема дай
do it tomorrow Why let's
давай завтра сделаем Зачем
prove it's not realistic, we'll prove to each
докажем не реально вот докажем друг
other Yes, this is nothing, this is nothing proof
другу Да это ничего это ничего не доказ
Why in democracy  in a Democratic
Почему в демократи в Демократической
country Look, I can in my country I wo
стране Смотри я могу в своей стране не
n’t give I won’t give I won’t give I’m telling you now I’m a
дам не дам не дам я рассказываю тепер я
free person because you are a slave you are a
свободный человек потому что вы раб вы
slave you must listen to me a free
раб вы меня должны послушать свободного
person maybe you’ll gain wisdom I can take it
человека может мудрости наберёте я могу
in my groan and go out and I can go out
в своей стоне взять и выйти и могу выйти
I can go out with  with a white piece of paper and stand there and
могу выйти с белым листком и постоять и
I won’t get anything for it, and you’re afraid to
мне ничего за это не будет а вы боитесь
even go out because you know your head will be
даже выйти потому что вы знаете вас
wrapped up in the cops, look, did
башка зась вас закут в менты посмотри
people come out with a white piece of paper? Why are people
люди выходили с белым ли А почему люди
okay? Why did people detain people with a
хорошо Почему люди людей задерживали с
white piece of paper? Why Do you know how it
белым листочком Почему А знаете как это
happened?  How, well, tell me, people were
происходило Как а ну расскажите людей
detained, taken to the nearest
задерживали отводили на ближа пункта
police station, they checked their documents and
полиции вот проверяли документы и
released safely, or did it
отпускали благополучно или это было
happen directly? On what basis were they
происходило прям А на каком основани их
detained in a democratic society? Yes,
задерживали в демократическом обществе
where will they live? Let me
Да где зажи их не зажи
remind you that the act of detention Yes
напомню что акт задержания Да
implies something about What
подразумевает под собой како про Как
is it called good?  What is the name of this
называется хорошо Как называется этот
process that they were taken from the place where
процесс что их забирали с того места где
they were and taken to the police
они были и отводили в полицейский
station they were taken not to the police
участок их их отводили не в полицейский
station But to the nearest Police station I
участок А в ближащий пункт Полиции Я же
told you Well, this is a Police station and not a station Yes,
говор Ну это пункт Полиции а не участок
he understood or a mobile is a
понял он или мобильный это является
vehicle yes
транспортное средство да
Vots On what basis were they taken away so
Вотс На каком основании их отводили так
as
в
to carry out to carry out a violation of
чтобы претворить претворить нарушение
the law what a violation of the law what a
закона какого нарушение закона в чём
violation of the law standing yes Tell me
нарушение закона стояние да Скажите В
what a violation of the law yes any action
чём нарушение закона да любое действие
Yes some citizens can
Да какими-то гражданами может
be regarded in Russian regarded yes
быть расценено по-русски расценено да
regarded as some kind of negative in  on your
расценено как какой-то негатив в свою
side Yes, that’s all so that conflicts do not
сторону Да вот и всё чтобы конфликтов не
happen, what the police do, first of
случалось что делают полицейски в первую
all, they prevent conflict
очередь он предотвращает конфликтные
situations. This is exactly what our police
ситуации Вот именно этим Наша полиция
do. That is, I understand correctly
занимается То есть я правильно понимаю
that, for example, in technical countries.
что например ках тических странах
For example, if in France a person comes out
Например если во Франции человек выйдет
with just a white piece of paper, the police will take
просто с белым листочком полиция заберёт
him away and  will take it away to clarify
его и отведёт для выяснения
the circumstances. At best, the
обстоятельств Это в лучшем случае
police in France will take it away. The police in
заберёт полиция во Франции полиция во
France act in completely different
Франции действует Совершенно другими
ways. I will remind you that the police in
способами я напомню вам полиция в
Holland are also in France once again. Show
Голландии тоже во Франции ещё раз
me, show me at least one thing and
Покажите мне покажите мне хоть одно
admit your mistake. Show me at least
признать свою ошибку Покажите мне хоть
one video where the police in France are just
одно видео где полиция во Франции просто
a guy who stands alone with a white piece of paper
чувака который стоит с белым листочком
Yes, they take him away and take him away Show
один Да его забирают и уводят Покажи А
Why is it a propaganda program Show show
почему прога ва пропаганды покажи покажи
that a man is standing in France with a poster
что человек стоит во Франции с плакатом
and they take him to the police there Show And
а его там забирают в полицию Покажи А вы
you will find a similar video from Russia
вы найдёте аналогичное видео из России
from Russia I can tell you right now
из России есть вот прямо сейчас могу вам
find show there was a bunch of yes A bunch of people in
найти показать куча было да Куча и в
Khabarovsk and in Vladivostok they
Хабаровске бы и во Владивостоке
take away the pay was
забирают был
swim You can show me at least one
свим Вы можете показать мне хоть в одной
in America or France yes everything is crap
в Америке или в Франции да всё обосрался
Archie Yes, a free democrat and they rolled out
Арчи Да свободный демократ а раскатали
I like to roll out such monsters, they just
люблю таких уродов раскатывать просто да
sit there  the rotten part of
сидят вот это самая гнилая часть
society, yes, there are people who understand
общества да есть люди которые понимают
they are in the position Yes, they are silent and think
они в рас положе Да они молча и думают
how it is, or at least will not support this
как это или хотя бы не поддержит этот
system Yes, but it’s on such people that the Nit rests Yes,
строй Да а вот на таких Гнида и держится
this is the whole Imperial regime he
Да вот этот весь Имперский режим он
talks about Yes, yes, you’re afraid, you kun
рассказывает Да что Да ты боишься ты кун
I  can I in my country? Yes, I can go out with a
я могу я в моей стране Да могу выйти с
white piece of paper and stand and shout. The white
белым листочком постоять покричать белый
piece of paper will not look at anything. Just
листок ничего не будет посмотрим Просто
like some guy, why is he yelling with a white
как на какого-то типа да что он с белым
piece of paper? Yes, and nothing will happen,
листком орёт Да ти и ничего не будет да
because I’m a free person in a
потому что я свободный человек в
free country, and you  white piece of paper you
свободной стране а ты белым листком ты
're crap to even think about it, yes,
обосрался даже подумать про это да
because the dude tells us in all seriousness
потому что чувак на полном серьёзе
that the police don't
рассказывает нам что полиция не
detain, they just take
задерживает она просто берёт уводит
the person to the nearest police station,
человека в ближайшее отделение полиции
not to the police station, not to the police station, but
не в участок не в полицейский участок А
to the nearest police station. Yes, not the police station,
в ближайшее отделение полиции Да не
but the nearest police station. Yes.
участок а ближайшее отделение полиции Да
to check his documents there
чтоб проверить там его документы да На
yes On the basis of what law This is
основании какого закона Вот это Это
just damn it today just amazing write
просто блин сегодня просто офигест пись
on th Telegram right now axis VN
на й Telegram прям зараз ось ВН
apok tse more and more respectfully YouTube taking
апок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
us through skarg or in your ban and I
нас через скарг ор в твый бан и дуже
don’t show too many videos to people at the moment
багато вдео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about the stream Tom for this
показуе информация про стрими Тому для
purpose, you need to write a Mali operational link
того щоб ми Мали оперативный звязок
right away and while there in telegra okm
пишиться прямо зараз а пок там в телегра
video sche tezh Tsikava and Korisna
окм видео ще теж цикава и корисна
information and we are guilty of you trimati
информация и мы повинни з вами тримати
postiyny operational link
постийний оперативный звязок
in the same time, show you the process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Glory to Ukraine
YouTube Слава Украине
write
пиши